<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rsockets on Collaboration In Encapsulation</title>
    <link>http://coinen.space/rsocket/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rsockets on Collaboration In Encapsulation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/OlegDokuka&#34;&gt;Oleh Dokuka&lt;/a&gt; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 23:05:08 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://coinen.space/rsocket/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How-To: Create RSocket-Java Receiver/Connector</title>
      <link>http://coinen.space/rsocket/posts/how-to-rsocket-java-receiver-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 23:05:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://coinen.space/rsocket/posts/how-to-rsocket-java-receiver-connector/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Acknowledgment Declaring Core Dependency Constructing RSocket Receiver Declaring Transport Dependency Constructing RSocket Receiver Transport Constructing RSocket Connector Complete Sample Summary What is next?   Acknowledgment This is a first blog post in the series of How to get started with RSocket related blog posts in which I&amp;#8217;m going to share the most straightforward tips on running, configuring, and debugging RSocket.
 This series of blog posts do not include the motivation of the RSocket itself which will be delivered in a separate series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-To: Send first messages in RSocket-Java</title>
      <link>http://coinen.space/rsocket/posts/how-to-rsocket-java-basic-interaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 23:05:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://coinen.space/rsocket/posts/how-to-rsocket-java-basic-interaction/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Acknowledgment Working With Payload Building communication with RSocket Building Request-Response interaction Implementing Fire and Forget Implementing Request Stream and Request Channel Summary What is next?   Acknowledgment This is the second blog post in the series of How to get started with RSocket related blog posts in which I&amp;#8217;m going to share the most straightforward tips on running, configuring, and debugging RSocket.
 In this blog post, I&amp;#8217;m going to share some necessary information about existing communication models in RSocket and how to start using them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>